Hi, and this lesson, I will show you how works Godlances feature from Windsor.
So this feature will give you one-click buttons above your code.
Let me select something like "explain refactor" and "add dog string".
You can use this quickly, "quick AI actions" to explain the code to refactor code
and add some documentation.
So, let's start with "explain".
What it does, so when you select, when you put your cursor on any class or method or variable,
you can click "explain" and it sends your request inside that code to the cascade,
and cascade opens a new chart.
And you will give you some clear explanation.
What it does.
So, it can be useful for some quickly understanding code,
which you don't really understand well.
For example, for some, if you work on some big project,
which is new for you, so you can have to explain the code.
And what else?
You can use the refactor.
So, when you click "refactor", the wind source will give you some really popular actions,
which other people do with AI.
For example, you can add some comments.
You can add console-ox statements to do some debugging.
You can clean up this code.
You can check for bugs on new pointers.
You can implement some code for the to-do comment,
with some feature which you want to add later.
And generate unit tests, make this code strongly typed, add some TypeScript support.
You can make this faster and more efficient.
You can make this code a functional red component.
I don't know why it's in it.
Normally, we use the hooks.
But maybe for some projects, it can be useful.
You can use a sync away instead of promises.
Yep.
And you can comment this code.
So, just explaining what is going on on this code.
So, let's use this one.
I selected everything.
Ooh.
There's a lot of comments right here.
Yeah.
Okay.
Now we see it was added.
Oh, nice.
Oh, oh.
For example, we can select another method.
Oh, let's have the gets-trans-identified indicator.
And let's choose add dog string.
Oh, when I click on it.
It will create some documentation like just dog.
And we'll follow the correct format for the different programming languages.
And you see it's the command zero tool of the function.
And also what it does.
So, we can accept it.
So, quick summary, when you can use code lenses to make some path for changes
while coding.
So, we just can click this action instead of selecting the part of code,
explaining that you want to please explain how it works.
You can just click on bottom.
It's really fast.
You can create tests early to keep some strong coverage because the refactor option
also will be to generate some unit tests.
You can write some documentation.
So, to make it easier for the rest of the team to understand it.
And you can also apply some refactor suggestions to clean up with just improve your code.
So, I hope it was useful for you.
Stay with me in the next lessons.